<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpp.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 06:53:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpp.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. It is an honor to be the Director of this beloved school, the very school that my own children attended and was our “home” for so many years. I am thrilled to now be part of your family’s journey through Zion’s Hill. We are a true community of teachers, parents, grandparents, and caregivers uniting to provide a nurturing and unique preschool experience. Children (and families!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Mission ZHPP fosters and facilitates children to become lifelong learners through exploration, discovery, imagination, and creativity.
In partnership with family and community, we provide a developmentally appropriate, nurturing, and secure setting promoting each child’s unique ability to reach their social, intellectual, and academic potential.
 The purpose of Zion’s Hill Preschool Program is to provide a center for the education of preschool children. The age-appropriate curriculum is designed to meet the social, emotional, physical, and intellectual needs of early childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testimonials</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:48:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>We found ZHPP during a time of need. We&amp;rsquo;d just moved to Wilton, and while our son&amp;rsquo;s birthdate qualified him for kindergarten, he needed more time to build skills, confidence, and socialization. Enter ZHPP! We enrolled him in the 5&amp;rsquo;s class and it was the best decision we could have made. Our son is now a thriving first grader. ZHPP is an amazing community, devoted to each and every child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Our Staff</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/meet-our-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:51:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/meet-our-staff/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:15:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/policies/</guid>
      <description>General The following is information regarding the procedures and general operation of our school. Please call the school if you have any questions.
Program Hours  Morning program – 9:00 am to 12:30 pm Extensions (Afternoon Adventures) offered Monday–Friday until 3 pm Doors open at 8:55 am Children must be picked up promptly each day at the end of their program or extension time.  Sign In and Out Following is the daily procedure for signing in/out your child:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit ZHPP</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/about/open-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:49:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/about/open-house/</guid>
      <description>We invite you to visit!
Come see first-hand what purposeful play means at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. Take a peak into our classrooms, meet our amazing teachers, and get a glimpse of what a day in the life looks like at our community-oriented school.
Open House
Saturday, January 4, 2020, 10–12
Five’s Class Information Session
Wednesday, January 15, 2020, 9:30am</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/parents/fundraising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:55:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/parents/fundraising/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/programs/curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:51:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/programs/curriculum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpp.org/news-blog/post-2020-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpp.org/news-blog/post-2020-09/</guid>
      <description>August 31 Meet the Teacher
September 1 Meet the Teacher 2 Board Meeting, 8:00 pm, Zoom 2-4 Orientation Week 7 No School – Labor Day 8-11 School Begins, 9:00–11:30, each day 14 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *14 Afternoon Adventures Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 12:30–3:00 *14 Early Bird Begins, 8 or 8:30 am 21 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *21 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30–3:00 28 No School – Yom Kippur</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>