<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 06:53:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpporg.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:37:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/calendar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:51:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/curriculum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. It is an honor to be the Director of this beloved school, the very school that my own children attended and was our “home” for so many years. I am thrilled to now be part of your family’s journey through Zion’s Hill. We are a true community of teachers, parents, grandparents, and caregivers uniting to provide a nurturing and unique preschool experience. Children (and families!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZHPP Board</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/zhpp-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/zhpp-board/</guid>
      <description>Welcome letter On behalf of the Board of Directors, welcome to Zion’s Hill Preschool Program! The board is a group of dedicated parent volunteers who use their skills, talents, and experience to make Zion’s Hill the best preschool that it can be. Parents join the Board for various reasons – to be more involved in the school’s community, to better understand their child’s pre-school education, to give back to the school for all it does for their kids, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/twos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/twos/</guid>
      <description>Two years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:4
2, 3, or 5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 This program is designed to help children separate from their parents, learn to take directions from another adult, become part of a group, and socialize with their peers.
 Daily activities include free play, music, finger plays, singing and stories, puzzles, table games, circle time, and art projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Mission ZHPP fosters and facilitates children to become lifelong learners through exploration, discovery, imagination, and creativity.
In partnership with family and community, we provide a developmentally appropriate, nurturing, and secure setting promoting each child’s unique ability to reach their social, intellectual, and academic potential.
 The purpose of Zion’s Hill Preschool Program is to provide a center for the education of preschool children. The age-appropriate curriculum is designed to meet the social, emotional, physical, and intellectual needs of early childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/threes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:42:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/threes/</guid>
      <description>Three years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:6
3 or 5 days a week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 Zion’s Hill offers a stimulating preschool program for three-year-olds, which concentrates on the development of independence, self-discipline, and peer cooperation.
 The children enjoy creative art, music, and cooking projects. Classrooms contain age-appropriate materials for improving attention span, developing coordination, fostering creativity, and building language skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testimonials</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:48:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>We found ZHPP during a time of need. We&amp;rsquo;d just moved to Wilton, and while our son&amp;rsquo;s birthdate qualified him for kindergarten, he needed more time to build skills, confidence, and socialization. Enter ZHPP! We enrolled him in the 5&amp;rsquo;s class and it was the best decision we could have made. Our son is now a thriving first grader. ZHPP is an amazing community, devoted to each and every child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/fundraising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:55:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/fundraising/</guid>
      <description>The cost of providing an educational and exciting environment for each student is not covered by tuition alone.
Please make a donation today via the PayPal button to support our kids, our teachers and our future. Thank you in advance for your kind contribution and participation.
Zion’s Hill Preschool is a 501(c) 3; all donations made to the school are tax deductible.
  Annual Spring Fling Fundraiser Friday April 24, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:43:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fours/</guid>
      <description>Four years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:8
4 or 5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 Zion’s Hill offers a program for four-year-olds that focuses on preschoolers’ expanding interest in the environment and their rapidly developing social skills.
 The program stresses kindergarten readiness. Subjects for exploration include family, community, occupations, transportation, and safety. In addition, music, art, creative movement, cooking, and woodworking offer many opportunities to express creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:38:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Part of what makes the community here at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program so special and unique are the families, local businesses, and groups volunteering their time and various services.
These contributions help create the foundation of what our program is all about. They illustrate the generosity present here at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program.
We would like to take a moment to extend a warm “thank you” to you.
We are grateful for each of your generous contributions throughout the school year here at ZHPP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:15:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/policies/</guid>
      <description>General The following is information regarding the procedures and general operation of our school. Please call the school if you have any questions.
Program Hours  Morning program – 9:00 am to 12:30 pm Extensions (Afternoon Adventures) offered Monday–Friday until 3 pm Doors open at 8:55 am Children must be picked up promptly each day at the end of their program or extension time.  Sign In and Out Following is the daily procedure for signing in/out your child:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:45:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fives/</guid>
      <description>Five years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:6
5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm M, W, F
9:00 am to 3:00 pm T, Th
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm on M, W, F
 Zion’s Hill has a program for five-year-olds specifically designed to foster independence and social development, while promoting higher learning within the classroom.
The program’s unique curriculum allows teachers to design a plan for each child based on individual strengths, challenges, and interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visit ZHPP</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/open-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:49:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/open-house/</guid>
      <description>We invite you to visit!
Come see first-hand what purposeful play means at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. Take a peak into our classrooms, meet our amazing teachers, and get a glimpse of what a day in the life looks like at our community-oriented school.
Open House
Saturday, January 4, 2020, 10–12
Five’s Class Information Session
Wednesday, January 15, 2020, 9:30am</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Bird</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/breakfast-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:47:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/breakfast-club/</guid>
      <description>Early Bird allows parents to drop off their child at 8:00 or 8:30 am, before the start of our core program. Parents are welcome to send breakfast for their child.
 24-hour notice is requested to register for this program. The perfect program if you need support managing challenging schedules! The cost is $14 per hour (8–9 am) or $8 per half hour (8:30–9 am). Please stop by the office for registration forms and details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Adventures and Extensions</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/afternoon-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:49:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/afternoon-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon Adventures Choose the day or days that appeal to your budding adventurer.
Afternoon Adventures, our wonderful extended day programs for the Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s, are designed so your child can learn, play, and explore.
The teachers plan theme-based activities for the children to delve into for the extended afternoon.
Afternoon Adventures include theme-focused activities, snack, and playground time.
The program runs from 12:30 to 3:00 pm each weekday for Three’s and Four’s, and from 12:30 to 3:00 pm on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays for Five’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Events</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:53:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-events/</guid>
      <description>Zion’s Hill Preschool Program strongly encourages family interaction and inclusion.
Understanding that every family is busy, we provide many options for involvement in school activities. There are annual events that parents and families can participate in throughout the school year.
Our special events are a part of our annual planning year to year so each child in the family may participate in these memorable activities. Our school community has always been very supportive of our school activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Camp</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/summer-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:56:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/summer-program/</guid>
      <description>Zion’s Hill Preschool Program will not offer Summer Camp program in year 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Programs</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:57:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-programs/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the year, ZHPP schedules special programming to enhance our classroom curriculum.
These may include movement and music programs, a school-wide hayride, both marine and furry animal visits, science programs, and visits from the town fire and police departments.
ZHPP makes an effort to ensure that these programs are age-appropriate and available to as many of the children as possible.
 Music 1x monthly Yoga 1x monthly Spanish 2x monthly Masterpiece Arts in the Four’s, and Five’s Animal Embassy Hayride Farm animals Community workers (dentist, police, and doctors) Fire truck visit Woodcock Nature Center for the Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s (twice a year for hibernation and awakenings) Maritime Center Bread and Movement for the Four’s and Five’s School bus ride for the Four’s and Five’s Special field trips for the Four’s and Five’s  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vicky Gibson</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/vicky-gibson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:01:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/vicky-gibson/</guid>
      <description>Spanish Born in Argentina, Vicky taught English as a foreign language in Buenos Aires before moving to the United States to pursue graduate work. With an MA in Bilingual Education from Fairfield University, she combines her native language with her love of education, children and music, to teach Spanish through music and movement. In addition to teaching at Zion’s Hill Preschool, Vicky runs Spanish classes for children PK–5 through Wilton Parks and Recreation and tutors high-school Spanish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracey Lajoie</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/tracey-lajoie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:01:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/tracey-lajoie/</guid>
      <description>Four&amp;rsquo;s Tracey joined Zion’s Hill Preschool in 2016, bringing with her 29 years of early childhood education experience. She previously taught three- and four-year-olds at a private school in Stamford. She has a BA in Psychology/Child Development from Quinnipiac College. Tracey’s teaching motto is, “Together we may give our children the roots to grow and the wings to fly.” Teaching is an adventure for Tracey. She loves the students’ smiles, curiosity, amazement, learning, and wonder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Harris</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/sarah-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:01:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/sarah-harris/</guid>
      <description>Four&amp;rsquo;s With a degree in psychology from Mount Holyoke College, Sarah joined the ZHPP family in 2007. She has years of experience raising her three children and volunteering in the community. Sarah loves to observe her students’ enthusiasm and joy for life. She enjoys exercising, gardening, and hand crafts such as sewing and rug-hooking. Sarah lived in Ridgefield with her husband, Paul, and children, Sam, Elizabeth, and Margaret.
Favorite children’s book: The Poky Little Puppy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sally Healy</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/sally-healy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:01:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/sally-healy/</guid>
      <description>Five&amp;rsquo;s Sally is originally from Michigan and has a BS in Finance from Boston College and an MBA from Fordham University. In 2014, she joined Zion’s Hill Preschool, where she loves to help children grow and expand their knowledge in partnership with their families. Reading, gardening, and walking are some of her favorite activities. She lives in Wilton with her husband, Thom, and their children, Sarah, Elizabeth, and Nancy.
Favorite children’s book: Madeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meg Donahue</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/meg-donahue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:01:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/meg-donahue/</guid>
      <description>Four&amp;rsquo;s Meg came to Zion’s Hill Preschool as a parent before becoming a regular sub and then a staff member in 2017. Meg has a BA in Economics from the University of Connecticut. She also spent many years as an Emergency Medical Technician for the FDNY and brings expertise in first aid and conflict resolution to the school. Providing a safe and positive learning environment is critical to Meg’s teaching philosophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marissa Generoso</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/marissa-generoso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/marissa-generoso/</guid>
      <description>Five&amp;rsquo;s With more than 25 years of experience teaching children ages two through six, Marissa joined Zion’s Hill Preschool in 2016. She holds an AD in Early Childhood Education from Norwalk Community College. Marissa focuses on each child’s strengths to help them feel confident and comfortable in achieving their goals, and she relishes children’s lit-up faces when they do! Marissa’s home in Norwalk is full: husband Carl, children Dax, Mia, and Tanner, and five dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louise Kaczmarek</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/louise-kaczmarek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/louise-kaczmarek/</guid>
      <description>Three&amp;rsquo;s Louise started at ZHPP as a floater in 2005, progressed to an assistant teacher position, and became lead teacher in the Three’s in 2013. Louise loves nothing more than opening young minds to the wonders of the world and showing children the fun in learning. She is a graduate of McGill University in Montreal and lives in Weston with her husband, Tom, her children, Evie, Adele, and John, and her dog, Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz Kaliski</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/liz-kaliski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/liz-kaliski/</guid>
      <description>Floater After three years as a parent, Liz joined the Zion’s Hill Preschool faculty in 2019. She holds a degree in sociology and criminal justice from Mount Saint Mary’s University. Liz is drawn to teaching because of “the happiness and wonder in children and the joy in watching them learn something new.” She lives in Darien with her husband, Drew, and children, Grady, Sean, and Kelly.
Favorite children’s book: Where the Wild Things Are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Drabaski</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/kathy-drabaski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/kathy-drabaski/</guid>
      <description>Four&amp;rsquo;s and Floater Kathy joined ZHPP in 2000, bringing 24 years of previous early childhood experience. She holds a BS in Early Childhood Education from Central Connecticut State University and has participated in NAEYC conferences as well as the Yale Early Childhood Study. She enjoys sharing with students her love of animals, nature, and being outdoors. Kathy relishes the “ah-ha” moment, when a child figures something out, solves a problem, or learns a new skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen Luchetta</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/karen-luchetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/karen-luchetta/</guid>
      <description>Two&amp;rsquo;s Karen joined the ZHPP staff in 2016. She graduated from the University of Rhode Island where she earned a BS in Fashion Merchandising and Design. Teaching is a rewarding experience for Karen. She loves contributing to the learning and growing that her students do every day. Karen lives in Wilton with family: Kevin, Riley, Ryan, and dog, Rascal.
Favorite children’s book: The Little Engine That Could. “This book shows kids that they should never give up, even if they’re small.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jo Anne Parady</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/jo-anne-parady/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/jo-anne-parady/</guid>
      <description>Music and Yoga Jo Anne teaches music and yoga at Zion’s Hill Preschool and loves every minute. With a dance and theater background, she started teaching “Music, Movement and Creative Dramatics for Toddlers and Preschoolers” many years ago at the Demonstration School of National College of Education in Wilmette, Illinois, where she was Director of the Movement Center. After moving with her family to Connecticut, she established her program in Greenwich, Stamford, and Wilton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenny Blumenfeld</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/jenny-blumenfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:59:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/jenny-blumenfeld/</guid>
      <description>Three&amp;rsquo;s Before joining ZHPP in 2014, Jenny taught kindergarten in Rye, New York, for 13 years. She holds a BA in business management and an MA in elementary education. She loves teaching the Three’s, where she instills in her students confidence and joy. Jenny is an avid baker and lives in Weston with her husband, Scott, and three children, Katie, Kyle, and Ethan.
Favorite childhood book: Brown Bear, Brown Bear. “This book elicits so many teaching opportunities, while being fun and entertaining for young children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diane McAdams</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/diane-mcadams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:59:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/diane-mcadams/</guid>
      <description>Floater After her children attended Zion’s Hill Preschool, Diane joined the staff in 2008. She holds a BBA from Pace University. Diane loves to encourage children to do their best, especially when trying to skills and activities. Born and raised in New York, Diane now lives in Wilton with her family.
Favorite children’s book: The Snowy Day. “I grew up in Queens, and my first best friend was my friend Pauline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deb Runestad</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/deb-runestad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:59:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/deb-runestad/</guid>
      <description>Two&amp;rsquo;s Deb holds a Bachelor of General Studies from the University of CT, as well as a Child Development certificate from Norwalk Community College. Deb also has extensive experience in theater with children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Danielle Wearing</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/danielle-wearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:59:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/danielle-wearing/</guid>
      <description>Tow&amp;rsquo;s Danielle holds a BA in Psychology from Holy Cross, an MA in Organizational Psychology from Teachers College, and an MS in Early Childhood Education from Bank Street College. She has been on the ZHPP faculty since 2017. Danielle loves that in the Two’s, she is one of the children’s very first teachers. She enjoys covering the important basics of being a kind member of the classroom community. Danielle lives in New Canaan, where she rides her Peloton bike, reads, watches baseball, and plays with her two dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christine Smith</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/christine-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:58:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/christine-smith/</guid>
      <description>Five&amp;rsquo;s and Masterpiece Christine started at ZHPP in 2005. She holds a BA in Government from Hamilton College and has extensive experience as a summer camp instructor and activity director. Christine teaches the highly successful Masterpiece art and music program to the Four’s and Five’s. Christine loves cooking, gardening, and water sports such as boating, sailing, and swimming. She lives in Ridgefield with her husband, Peter, and three daughters, Emily, Caroline, and Elizabeth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bridget Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/bridget-mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:58:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/bridget-mitchell/</guid>
      <description>Three&amp;rsquo;s Bridget holds an AS degree in Early Childhood Education from Empire State College. She also has a strong background in theater, with a degree from Lee Strasberg Theater Institute. She started teaching at Zion’s Hill Preschool in 2015. In the classroom, she loves watching the children grow throughout the year, form friendships, become independent, and take in the world around them. Swimming, letter boxing, and photography keep her busy outside of school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brenda Marchi</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/brenda-marchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:58:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/brenda-marchi/</guid>
      <description>Assistant Director Brenda holds a BA in Psychology from St. Michael’s College. She joined the ZHPP family in 2004, where she has worked with all age groups and now serves as Assistant Director. Brenda loves bowling and Scrabble and watching the ZHPP students discover new things about life and themselves. She lives in Wilton with her family: Justin, Elizabeth, John, and Benjamin.
Favorite children’s book: The Giving Tree. “I love the book, though I didn’t read it until college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anne Gaston</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/anne-gaston/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/anne-gaston/</guid>
      <description>Four&amp;rsquo;s Anne joined ZHPP as a parent before becoming a staff member in 2001. She earned her BA in Dance from SUNY and MA in Early Childhood from Adelphi University. Her sheer love of being with kids compelled her to become a teacher. Anne loves walking, running, and spinning, and lives in Wilton with her husband, Fred, and their four daughters, Phoebe, Zoe, Keiley, and Sophie. A dog, two cats, and two frogs complete Anne’s big family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Soule</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/anna-soule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 23:46:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/about/meet-our-staff/anna-soule/</guid>
      <description>Two&amp;rsquo;s Anna joined the Zion’s Hill Preschool faculty in 2007. Before that, she was an active parent with two children attending the program. Anna holds an AS in Early Childhood Education. She loves working with the two-year-olds because of their curiosity, eagerness to learn, and growth into capable human beings. Anna loves running, reading, cooking, and her dog. She grew up in Sweden and now lives in Wilton with her husband, Larry, and children, Victoria and Christopher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directions</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/contact/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 09:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/contact/directions/</guid>
      <description>Get In Touch Tel: (203) 762-9620
Fax: (203) 761-8619
Email: zhpp@optonline.net
Address Zion&amp;rsquo;s Hill Preschool Program
470 Danbury Road
Wilton, CT 06897

View Larger Map Get directions »</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020-2021 Price Sheet</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/registration/2020-2021-price-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 14:25:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/registration/2020-2021-price-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Registration Fee $200.00 for first child; $75.00 each additional child.
Core Program Fees Two&amp;rsquo;s
     Annual Per Payment     2-Days Program $4,490 $ 1,122.50   3-Days Program $6,730 $1,682.50   5-Day Program $11,220 $2,805.00    Three’s
     Annual Per Payment     3-Day Program $5,250 $1,312.50   5-Day Program $8,750 $2,187.50    Four&amp;rsquo;s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/post-2020-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/post-2020-09/</guid>
      <description>August 31 Meet the Teacher
September 1 Meet the Teacher 2 Board Meeting, 8:00 pm, Zoom 2-4 Orientation Week 7 No School – Labor Day 8-11 School Begins, 9:00–11:30, each day 14 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *14 Afternoon Adventures Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 12:30–3:00 *14 Early Bird Begins, 8 or 8:30 am 21 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *21 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30–3:00 28 No School – Yom Kippur</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</guid>
      <description>They came with diplomas. They came with cookies and cameras. They came with a big banner and binders full of art. And they came with a bridge. A five-foot-long arched wooden bridge.
With schools closed, and current guidelines limiting indoor gatherings to 10 and outdoor events to 25, the usual graduation plans are abandoned everywhere. Planning committees are finding ways to honor 2020’s high school and college graduates with pre-recorded speeches and Zoom calls and yard signs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>