<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parents on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parents on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:54:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:37:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/calendar/</guid>
      <description>2020-2021 School Calendar August  31 Meet the Teacher  September  1 Meet the Teacher 2-4 Orientation Week 7 No School – Labor Day 8-11 School Begins, 9:00–11:30, each day 14 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm 14 Afternoon Adventures Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 12:30–3:00 21 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm 21 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30–3:00 28 No School – Yom Kippur  October  9 No Afternoon Adventures/Extensions 12 No School – Columbus Day 15 Tuition Payment Due, 2nd Installment 15 Parent Open House 20-21 Photo Days  November  3 No School – Election Day 25-27 No School – Thanksgiving Break  December  23 No Afternoon Adventures/Extensions 24-31 No School – Holiday Break  January  1 No School – New Year’s Day 4 School Resumes 4 Open Enrollment/Registration Begins for 2021–2022 School Year 15 Tuition Payment Due, 3rd Installment 18 No School – Martin Luther King Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZHPP Board</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/zhpp-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/zhpp-board/</guid>
      <description>Welcome letter On behalf of the Board of Directors, welcome to Zion’s Hill Preschool Program! The board is a group of dedicated parent volunteers who use their skills, talents, and experience to make Zion’s Hill the best preschool that it can be. Parents join the Board for various reasons – to be more involved in the school’s community, to better understand their child’s pre-school education, to give back to the school for all it does for their kids, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/fundraising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:55:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/fundraising/</guid>
      <description>The cost of providing an educational and exciting environment for each student is not covered by tuition alone.
Please make a donation today via the PayPal button to support our kids, our teachers and our future. Thank you in advance for your kind contribution and participation.
Zion’s Hill Preschool is a 501(c) 3; all donations made to the school are tax deductible.
  Annual Spring Fling Fundraiser Friday April 24, 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 16:38:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/parents/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Part of what makes the community here at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program so special and unique are the families, local businesses, and groups volunteering their time and various services.
These contributions help create the foundation of what our program is all about. They illustrate the generosity present here at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program.
We would like to take a moment to extend a warm “thank you” to you.
We are grateful for each of your generous contributions throughout the school year here at ZHPP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>