<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:02:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-09/</guid>
      <description>August 31 Meet the Teacher
September 1 Meet the Teacher 2 Board Meeting, 8:00 pm, Zoom 2-4 Orientation Week 7 No School – Labor Day 8-11 School Begins, 9:00–11:30, each day 14 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *14 Afternoon Adventures Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 12:30–3:00 *14 Early Bird Begins, 8 or 8:30 am 21 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *21 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30–3:00 28 No School – Yom Kippur</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</guid>
      <description>They came with diplomas. They came with cookies and cameras. They came with a big banner and binders full of art. And they came with a bridge. A five-foot-long arched wooden bridge.
With schools closed, and current guidelines limiting indoor gatherings to 10 and outdoor events to 25, the usual graduation plans are abandoned everywhere. Planning committees are finding ways to honor 2020’s high school and college graduates with pre-recorded speeches and Zoom calls and yard signs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-05/</guid>
      <description>Treat Yourself Right Dear Families,
Happy May! Let’s hope that April showers bring May flowers—and with it some warmer temperatures, a flattening of the COVID curve or better yet a vaccine, and some return to normalcy! These are trying times. I am finding the uncertainty particularly difficult to grasp: how long will social distancing—as necessary as it is—last? When can our school/town/state/country/world safely reopen? Will summer camp proceed?
These questions weigh heavily, as many have been suddenly thrust into roles we never envisioned (home school headmaster, short order cook, closet organizer, peacekeeper, internet troubleshooter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZHPP Board Slate and Annual Meeting – 2020-2021</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/board-slate-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 13:31:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/board-slate-2020/</guid>
      <description>Every year around this time, the ZHPP Board of Directors accepts applications in order to build the slate for next year’s Board. This slate is then voted on at the Annual Meeting of Zion’s Hill Preschool Program, Inc., held in May.
This year’s Annual Meeting will be held via Zoom on Wednesday, May 6th at 7:30 pm, and all families are invited to attend. A Zoom invitation will be sent prior to the meeting time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-04/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Well, as you might have guessed, this is an unusual newsletter, brought to you at this most unusual time. It is hard to believe that we were all together just over two weeks ago, and that our daily lives have changed so dramatically in such a short period of time. Who would have thought that I would miss my family’s harried morning rush to get to the bus and school on time, or juggling our activities and (gasp!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-03/</guid>
      <description>Happy March!
Dear Families,
The third month of the year is upon us—or is it? Fun fact: the ancient Roman calendar included just ten months, beginning with March and ending with December. In many ways, March brings new beginnings as we say goodbye to winter and hello to spring. The days grow longer, the sun shines brighter, icy patches melt to muddy puddles, and plants push their way through newly thawed ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-02/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Happy February! Winter may have been slow to arrive, but we finally have some SNOW! The children are enamored—they enjoy watching snowflakes fall outside the classroom windows, decorating the snowmen and snowflakes that brighten our halls, and, best of all, playing outdoors in the snow! The winter playgrounds provide an entirely different environment for the children to cooperatively explore. They love it! We hope you, too, will enjoy the snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Five&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/why-the-fives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/why-the-fives/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps your child’s birthday falls in the second half of the year. Maybe you’re thinking your child needs more social and emotional growth. Or you sense that your child would benefit from additional play-based learning before enrolling in kindergarten. Whatever the reason, you might be wondering, why the Five’s?
On January 15, a panel of staff, parents, and an education specialist, convened at Zion’s Hill Preschool to answer that question. Director Jessica Joy opened the event by providing some context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-01/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Happy New Year!
I hope this finds you enjoying the holiday break with opportunities for both relaxation and merriment with your loved ones. January is the perfect time to pause, take stock, and set goals for the year ahead. While we adults may see the New Year as a chance to test old patterns or try something new, the children will be settling into the comfort of school routines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Play—and Possibilities!—with Dough</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/endless-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/endless-play/</guid>
      <description>Making play dough is one of our favorite activities at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program … for children and teachers alike! But did you know that the original Play-Doh® was first made as a wallpaper cleaner in the 1930s? Upon learning that young children found modeling clay too difficult to manipulate, the manufacturer sent some of the pliable cleaning material to local schools in Cincinnati. Word quickly spread: the product was showcased at an education convention in 1955, and a year later, Play-Doh® was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-12/</guid>
      <description>Happy Holidays! Dear Families,
Say it isn’t so … is December nearly here? Time sure flies when you’re having fun, and we’ve certainly been having a lot of fun!
A highlight in November was the horse-drawn carriage. Over the wee hill and through the lot, to the church did we all go! I even got to ride with the children, a real treat. We celebrated our annual Thanksgiving Feast with our Four’s and Five’s families, a perennial favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do children gain writing skills through play?</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/writing-skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/writing-skill/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common questions I receive from prospective parents about our play-based program is, “How do children learn if they are playing all day?” It’s a fair question. As adults, we know how to read, write, add, and subtract, but we may have no recollection of how we learned these things. I certainly don’t! It’s very difficult to put ourselves back in the mindset of a child, to really understand what children experience as they learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-11/</guid>
      <description>Grateful in November Dear Families,
As October ends, we officially close the book on “back to school” mode, which culminated in our Fall Family Fun Day and Parent Open House. We loved seeing so many of you and showcasing our school. Picture Day has also come and gone—we can’t wait for you to see the happy, adorable faces! The children have adjusted to their classroom environments and are enjoying all of the “extras” ZHPP provides, from singing and downward-dogging with Miss JoAnne, to learning Spanish with Señora Vicky, to climbing on fire trucks during Fire Prevention Week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-10/</guid>
      <description>Happy Fall! Dear Families,
The school year is in full swing, and such fun fall will bring! The children have settled in beautifully to their classrooms and routines, and the staff and I have loved getting to know each of them—and you too! It is so heartwarming to see friendships forming, and the halls and classrooms once again filled with the children’s artwork and proud evidence of their learning (just a glimpse of what you will hear about at Open House!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-09/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Back! Dear Families,
Welcome to the 2019–2020 school year (our 47th year) at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program! We hope everyone had an amazingly memorable summer and we are excited to hear about your adventures.
The teachers and staff can’t wait to greet you on the playgrounds Tuesday and Wednesday, August 27 and 28. We’ve missed you so! Meet the Teacher Days will be followed by Orientation on Thursday and Friday, when we will share information about the classroom, curriculum, and daily routines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-06/</guid>
      <description>Happy Summer! Dear Parents,
It’s hard to believe we are in the home stretch, heading toward the finish line of another wonderful year at ZHPP! And speaking of finish line, how great was the Mini-Marathon?!?!? The children loved it and the special annual tradition allowed us to see how much growth – both physically and developmentally – has transpired this year. Year-end brings the perfect opportunity to celebrate our little learners, but it is bittersweet too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-05/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
It is certainly invigorating to see the green grass and daffodils (and even the dandelions) popping out of the moist soil — such a lush and welcomed sight. A special thank you to those who helped spruce up the playgrounds and yards at Spring Clean-up — everything looks great! The children love the outdoor spaces and are easily energized by fresh air and exercise… with special Zion’s Hill traditions in May they will have plenty of both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-04/</guid>
      <description>Knock, Knock
Who’s there?
Owls say
Owls say who?
Yes, they do.
Hee hee! No fooling, April is upon us – another month filled with laughter and fun! March was magical in its own right, with the first and only real snowfall of the year, and a special visit from Woodcock Nature Center. While Mr. Sam did not bring an owl, it was amazing to watch the wonder on the children’s faces as he presented his cast of characters… whether it was Chubbs (probably the biggest frog they had ever seen), Squirt the baby turtle, or the sticky-footed tree frog, they were totally delighted!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-03/</guid>
      <description>Looking Forward to Spring! Dear Families,
Happy March! This proverbial “In Like a Lion, Out Like a Lamb” month is filled with lots of changes and transformations as we say goodbye to winter and hello to spring…. the days grow longer, the sun shines brighter, icy patches melt to muddy puddles, and winter coats are replaced with lighter jackets. March is also metaphoric for the changes and transformations that the children have experienced since September… some back-to-school jitters have given way to smiles and laughter, they all have grown a little taller, expanded their vocabulary and friendships, and have their daily school routines down pat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-02/</guid>
      <description>Celebrations of Love! Dear Parents,
Happy February! The slow start to winter, with many sunny days, has helped everyone adjust to the colder temps, and the SNOW!! Despite the work involved donning winter gear, it’s always worth it and great for the kids to get fresh air! They love it, and find the playgrounds provide an entirely different environment in which to explore and cooperatively discover.
Indoors, we are gallivanting along with our wonderfully planned schedules and routines, along with some extra fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-01/</guid>
      <description>Dear Parents,
We hope this finds you well-satiated with food, drink, family and friends. January is a great time to hit the reset button – earlier bed times, house decluttering, and of course the infamous New Year’s resolutions to reverse holiday indulgences. It can be both motivating and invigorating to step outside our comfort zones and try something different; better yet, to encourage others along the way … Our talented teachers are proof positive of this as they gently guide the children along their learning journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-12/</guid>
      <description>Happy Holidays Dear Parents,
The view from our shared desk continues to be a roly, poly, smooth and exhilarating ride! So much diversity in a day, a week, the last month. Quiet times find us engaging with the kids in their classrooms, giving a tour and fine-tuning schedules. Busy times find us loading children onto a horse-drawn carriage for a hay ride, singing and dancing along with Miss Jo Anne and as always, working on communications with the staff, students and parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-10/</guid>
      <description>Let the Fall Fun Begin! From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
The school year is off to a great start! The children have had a smooth transition into their new classrooms and for many, into their new school as well. The teachers are having so much fun getting to know each and every one of them through home visits and classroom interactions. I was able to spend time in each of the classrooms and enjoyed all of the conversations with your little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-09/</guid>
      <description>Wow, that seemed like the fastest summer ever. It was so nice to see so many of our new families as well as returning families at our Summer Concert and the New Family Playdate…
 September Calendar  4-7 Orientation Week, 9:00-11:30am each day 5 Board Meeting, 7:30pm, Conference Room 10 No School – Rosh Hashanah 11 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00am-12:30pm 11 Afternoon Adventures Begin, (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s),12:30-3:00pm 17 2nd Tuition Payment Due 17 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00am-12:30pm 17 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30-3:00pm 19 No School – Yom Kippur 20-21 Pied Piper Petting Zoo 23 Fall Family Fun Day, 10:30am-12:30pm (Rain date: Oct 14) 27-28 Library 29 Parent Social, 7:30-10:30pm   From the Director’s Desk: Dear Families,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-06/</guid>
      <description>June Calendar  3 Family Fun Day, 10:30am-12:30pm 6 Board Meeting, 7:30pm 8 Last Day of Afternoon Adventures/Extensions 14 4′s and 5′s Graduation
Miss Marissa’s Class, 9:30-10:15am
Miss Kristen’s Class, 10:15-11:00am
Miss Molly’s Class, 11:00-11:45am 14-15 End-of-Year Picnics 18-22 Camp Week 1: Camping 25-29 Camp Week 2: Beach  Summer Awaits!
 From the Director’s Desk: Dear Families,
It’s nearly June, and as a Director, June is always a bittersweet month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-05/</guid>
      <description>May Calendar  1-2 Yoga 2 Annual Meeting, 7:30pm (Conference Room) 7-8 Spanish 7-11 Teacher Appreciation Week 15 2018-2019 Returning/New Families’ Contracts and 1st Tuition Payment Due 15-16 Music 16 Bike Day, 4′s and 5′s Only 17 Kindergarten Coffee, 9:15am (Conference Room) 20 Spring Family Fun Day, 10:30am -12:30pm 24-25 Library 25 Mini Marathon, 9:15am 28 No School – Memorial Day, But Join the Fun at Wilton Memorial Day Parade!  Marching Ahead to a Memorable May!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-04/</guid>
      <description>April Calendar  3-4 Yoga 4 Board Meeting, 7:30pm (Conference Room) 9-13 No School – Spring Break 16-20 Week of the Young Child 17-18 Music 20 Children’s Parade, 9:15am 20 Spring Fling, 7:00pm (Rolling Hills Country Club) 23-24 Spanish 25 Administrative Professionals Day 25 Volunteer Appreciation Breakfast 26-27 Library   From the Director’s Desk: April Showers Bring May Flowers
Dear Families,
March didn’t offer the best beginning to spring, but we made the most of it with special indoor activities like making Kool-Aid scented playdough, and a field trip to Ambler Farm for the 4′s and 5′s where they got to learn about maple sugaring and see brand new baby chicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-02/</guid>
      <description>Dates to Remember February  6 &amp;amp; 7 Yoga 10 Parents and Pastries, 9:30-11am 12 Valentine’s Day Teacher’s Luncheon 12 &amp;amp; 13 Spanish 13 &amp;amp; 14 Class Valentine’s Parties 16-19 No School – Winter Recess 20 &amp;amp; 21 Music 22 &amp;amp; 23 Wilton Library  March  1 &amp;amp; 2 Dr. Seuss Parent Read-Along 6 &amp;amp; 7 Yoga 12 &amp;amp; 13 Spanish 22 &amp;amp; 23 Wilton Library 27 &amp;amp; 28 Music 30 No School – Good Friday  A complete 2017-2018 school calendar has been posted on our website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2018</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2018-01/</guid>
      <description>From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
Welcome back and Happy New Year! I hope you all had a relaxing and enjoyable holiday season. It is hard to believe that this newsletter marks the 2nd anniversary of my tenure at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. The last year has been another year of joy, happiness, and true passion for my career in Early Childhood Education. I could not ask to be part of a more fantastic program than what you find at ZHPP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2017</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-12/</guid>
      <description>From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
November was another busy month, and Mother Nature gave us such beautiful weather to enjoy.
Our horse-drawn hay rides were a huge success on a fantastic fall day. The children admired the draft horses as we rode through the parking lots of the school and church. All of the children enjoyed another round of yoga, music, library, and Spanish, where Senora Vicky taught some words related to Thanksgiving!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2017</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-11/</guid>
      <description>From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
The month of October has been filled with so much fun and excitement. The children have been able to make many wonderful memories while exploring the ZHPP environment. Mother Nature has been throwing in her own surprises and we are taking full advantage of it with picnics, bike riding, nature walks, and extra outdoor time. It was so great to see so many of our parents attend the Open House on October 3rd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2017</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-10/</guid>
      <description>From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
The school year is off to a great start! The children have had a smooth transition into their new classrooms and for many, into their new school as well. The teachers are having so much fun getting to know each and every one of them through home visits and classroom interactions. I’ve been able to spend time in each of the classrooms and have enjoyed all the conversations with your little ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2017</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2017-09/</guid>
      <description>From the Director’s Desk: Dear Parents,
It is hard to believe, but summer has come to an end. I am so excited and honored to be starting my second full school year at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program. The summer at the school was very busy, as we redesigned some of the classroom spaces, incorporated new materials, and installed some cabinetry in our conference room.
The teachers are very excited to start using the new curriculum materials, including STEM materials.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>