<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 23:02:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-09/</guid>
      <description>August 31 Meet the Teacher
September 1 Meet the Teacher 2 Board Meeting, 8:00 pm, Zoom 2-4 Orientation Week 7 No School – Labor Day 8-11 School Begins, 9:00–11:30, each day 14 Full Days Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *14 Afternoon Adventures Begin (Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s), 12:30–3:00 *14 Early Bird Begins, 8 or 8:30 am 21 Full Days Begin (Two’s), 9:00 am–12:30 pm *21 Extensions Begin (Two’s), 12:30–3:00 28 No School – Yom Kippur</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/graduation-2020/</guid>
      <description>They came with diplomas. They came with cookies and cameras. They came with a big banner and binders full of art. And they came with a bridge. A five-foot-long arched wooden bridge.
With schools closed, and current guidelines limiting indoor gatherings to 10 and outdoor events to 25, the usual graduation plans are abandoned everywhere. Planning committees are finding ways to honor 2020’s high school and college graduates with pre-recorded speeches and Zoom calls and yard signs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-05/</guid>
      <description>Treat Yourself Right Dear Families,
Happy May! Let’s hope that April showers bring May flowers—and with it some warmer temperatures, a flattening of the COVID curve or better yet a vaccine, and some return to normalcy! These are trying times. I am finding the uncertainty particularly difficult to grasp: how long will social distancing—as necessary as it is—last? When can our school/town/state/country/world safely reopen? Will summer camp proceed?
These questions weigh heavily, as many have been suddenly thrust into roles we never envisioned (home school headmaster, short order cook, closet organizer, peacekeeper, internet troubleshooter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZHPP Board Slate and Annual Meeting – 2020-2021</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/board-slate-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 13:31:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/board-slate-2020/</guid>
      <description>Every year around this time, the ZHPP Board of Directors accepts applications in order to build the slate for next year’s Board. This slate is then voted on at the Annual Meeting of Zion’s Hill Preschool Program, Inc., held in May.
This year’s Annual Meeting will be held via Zoom on Wednesday, May 6th at 7:30 pm, and all families are invited to attend. A Zoom invitation will be sent prior to the meeting time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-04/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Well, as you might have guessed, this is an unusual newsletter, brought to you at this most unusual time. It is hard to believe that we were all together just over two weeks ago, and that our daily lives have changed so dramatically in such a short period of time. Who would have thought that I would miss my family’s harried morning rush to get to the bus and school on time, or juggling our activities and (gasp!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-03/</guid>
      <description>Happy March!
Dear Families,
The third month of the year is upon us—or is it? Fun fact: the ancient Roman calendar included just ten months, beginning with March and ending with December. In many ways, March brings new beginnings as we say goodbye to winter and hello to spring. The days grow longer, the sun shines brighter, icy patches melt to muddy puddles, and plants push their way through newly thawed ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-02/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Happy February! Winter may have been slow to arrive, but we finally have some SNOW! The children are enamored—they enjoy watching snowflakes fall outside the classroom windows, decorating the snowmen and snowflakes that brighten our halls, and, best of all, playing outdoors in the snow! The winter playgrounds provide an entirely different environment for the children to cooperatively explore. They love it! We hope you, too, will enjoy the snow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the Five&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/why-the-fives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/why-the-fives/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps your child’s birthday falls in the second half of the year. Maybe you’re thinking your child needs more social and emotional growth. Or you sense that your child would benefit from additional play-based learning before enrolling in kindergarten. Whatever the reason, you might be wondering, why the Five’s?
On January 15, a panel of staff, parents, and an education specialist, convened at Zion’s Hill Preschool to answer that question. Director Jessica Joy opened the event by providing some context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2019-12/</guid>
      <description>Dear Families,
Happy New Year!
I hope this finds you enjoying the holiday break with opportunities for both relaxation and merriment with your loved ones. January is the perfect time to pause, take stock, and set goals for the year ahead. While we adults may see the New Year as a chance to test old patterns or try something new, the children will be settling into the comfort of school routines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endless Play—and Possibilities!—with Dough</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/endless-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/endless-play/</guid>
      <description>Making play dough is one of our favorite activities at Zion’s Hill Preschool Program … for children and teachers alike! But did you know that the original Play-Doh® was first made as a wallpaper cleaner in the 1930s? Upon learning that young children found modeling clay too difficult to manipulate, the manufacturer sent some of the pliable cleaning material to local schools in Cincinnati. Word quickly spread: the product was showcased at an education convention in 1955, and a year later, Play-Doh® was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 00:12:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/newsletter-2020-01/</guid>
      <description>Happy Holidays!
Dear Families,
Say it isn’t so … is December nearly here? Time sure flies when you’re having fun, and we’ve certainly been having a lot of fun!
A highlight in November was the horse-drawn carriage. Over the wee hill and through the lot, to the church did we all go! I even got to ride with the children, a real treat. We celebrated our annual Thanksgiving Feast with our Four’s and Five’s families, a perennial favorite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do children gain writing skills through play?</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/writing-skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/news-blog/writing-skill/</guid>
      <description>One of the most common questions I receive from prospective parents about our play-based program is, “How do children learn if they are playing all day?” It’s a fair question. As adults, we know how to read, write, add, and subtract, but we may have no recollection of how we learned these things. I certainly don’t! It’s very difficult to put ourselves back in the mindset of a child, to really understand what children experience as they learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>