<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programs on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</title>
    <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programs on Zion&#39;s Hill Preschool Program</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:29:45 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:51:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/curriculum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/twos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:36:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/twos/</guid>
      <description>Two years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:4
2, 3, or 5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 This program is designed to help children separate from their parents, learn to take directions from another adult, become part of a group, and socialize with their peers.
 Daily activities include free play, music, finger plays, singing and stories, puzzles, table games, circle time, and art projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/threes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:42:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/threes/</guid>
      <description>Three years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:6
3 or 5 days a week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 Zion’s Hill offers a stimulating preschool program for three-year-olds, which concentrates on the development of independence, self-discipline, and peer cooperation.
 The children enjoy creative art, music, and cooking projects. Classrooms contain age-appropriate materials for improving attention span, developing coordination, fostering creativity, and building language skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:43:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fours/</guid>
      <description>Four years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:8
4 or 5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm daily
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm
 Zion’s Hill offers a program for four-year-olds that focuses on preschoolers’ expanding interest in the environment and their rapidly developing social skills.
 The program stresses kindergarten readiness. Subjects for exploration include family, community, occupations, transportation, and safety. In addition, music, art, creative movement, cooking, and woodworking offer many opportunities to express creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:45:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/fives/</guid>
      <description>Five years old by 12/31
Teacher:Child Ratio 1:6
5 days/week
9:00 am to 12:30 pm M, W, F
9:00 am to 3:00 pm T, Th
Optional extended day to 3:00 pm on M, W, F
 Zion’s Hill has a program for five-year-olds specifically designed to foster independence and social development, while promoting higher learning within the classroom.
The program’s unique curriculum allows teachers to design a plan for each child based on individual strengths, challenges, and interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Bird</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/breakfast-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:47:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/breakfast-club/</guid>
      <description>Early Bird allows parents to drop off their child at 8:00 or 8:30 am, before the start of our core program. Parents are welcome to send breakfast for their child.
 24-hour notice is requested to register for this program. The perfect program if you need support managing challenging schedules! The cost is $14 per hour (8–9 am) or $8 per half hour (8:30–9 am). Please stop by the office for registration forms and details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afternoon Adventures and Extensions</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/afternoon-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:49:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/afternoon-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Afternoon Adventures Choose the day or days that appeal to your budding adventurer.
Afternoon Adventures, our wonderful extended day programs for the Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s, are designed so your child can learn, play, and explore.
The teachers plan theme-based activities for the children to delve into for the extended afternoon.
Afternoon Adventures include theme-focused activities, snack, and playground time.
The program runs from 12:30 to 3:00 pm each weekday for Three’s and Four’s, and from 12:30 to 3:00 pm on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays for Five’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Events</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:53:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-events/</guid>
      <description>Zion’s Hill Preschool Program strongly encourages family interaction and inclusion.
Understanding that every family is busy, we provide many options for involvement in school activities. There are annual events that parents and families can participate in throughout the school year.
Our special events are a part of our annual planning year to year so each child in the family may participate in these memorable activities. Our school community has always been very supportive of our school activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Camp</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/summer-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:56:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/summer-program/</guid>
      <description>Zion’s Hill Preschool Program will not offer Summer Camp program in year 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Programs</title>
      <link>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:57:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zhpporg.github.io/programs/special-programs/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the year, ZHPP schedules special programming to enhance our classroom curriculum.
These may include movement and music programs, a school-wide hayride, both marine and furry animal visits, science programs, and visits from the town fire and police departments.
ZHPP makes an effort to ensure that these programs are age-appropriate and available to as many of the children as possible.
 Music 1x monthly Yoga 1x monthly Spanish 2x monthly Masterpiece Arts in the Four’s, and Five’s Animal Embassy Hayride Farm animals Community workers (dentist, police, and doctors) Fire truck visit Woodcock Nature Center for the Three’s, Four’s, and Five’s (twice a year for hibernation and awakenings) Maritime Center Bread and Movement for the Four’s and Five’s School bus ride for the Four’s and Five’s Special field trips for the Four’s and Five’s  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>